M. SAFDAR KHAN

ST. 5 Gunj Shakeer Town Pak-Pattan Road, Sahiwal 57000, Punjab, Pakistan * (+92) 348 7548001 * safdar@pakautonation.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Administrative IT Officer, Developer, Graphic Designer, Team Leader, AI Developer and Entrepreneur having 1 year of post qualification experience and total of 3+ year of work experience in the field of IT and Software. I have worked with databases from relational to NoSQL and Operational, Python, C#, PHP & Asp web Development, working as team member to team leader from the time of my university. Start my own software House as an entrepreneurial activity named as "The MSK inc." and lead a team of 5 members. Worked for Semi Gov. non profit Orgnization for 1 Year with different projects. That's why I've impeccable written and verbal skills, excellent skills of management, development, AI and robotics.

ABOUT AND SOCIAL LINKS

I'm Safdar Khan, graduated from **Comsats University** in BS(**Software Engineering**), worked for Pakistan Red Crescent (Semi. Gov. Organization) for different projects, decently work with small to large scale projects as a developer and designer. I'm about of 23 (15th of July 1997). I'm quiet, be like a homunculus but a quite hard worker and motivative, try to sort out the problems or predicaments related to me or people near my self; try to think positive, creative and be clear in any situation.

- ⊕ https://www.safdarkhan.ml 🐧
- https://fb.me/thesafdarkhan dthe_safdarkhan
- ♥ @theSafdarKhan

- @ safdarkhanofficial@gmail.com
- thesafdarkhan
- safdarkhanofficial

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Management Intern IT (MIS Developer) - Pakistan Red Crescent (NHQ Islamabad)

IT Intern and Software Developer, August 5 2019 - August 2 2020

Develop IMS - Inventory Management System as a single ton and implement solution for IT in PRCS - NHQ Islamabad.

UI Designer and Back-end Developer - ACMCS (Comsats University)

UI and Back-end Developer Intern, March 2018 - Nov. 2018

I have worked as internee of UI Designer and Backend developer in Association for Computing Machinery Comsats Sahiwal.

IT OFFICER(Consultant) - Poly Print Packages (Printing Press)

Consultant - Nov. 2016 - Dec. 2017

• I'd provided consultancy in network and IT services train new staff for Graphic Designing and Design Analysis. During this I period I'd learned a number of skills including socialization and earn some professional working experience. I'd work on Corel draw x7, Adobe Photoshop and techniques to capture RGB designs to vector designs and CMYK Collor combinations etc.

Graphic Designer - Poly Print Packages (Printing Press)

Intern - June 2016 - Sep. 2016

• I'd worked as Graphic Designing Intern during the vacations from university. That was a decent time to learn a lot of skills.

EDUCATION

COMSATS UNIVERSITY ISLAMABAD, SAHIWAL CAMPUS

Bachelor of Software Engineering, Sep. 2015 - July 2019 (3.36 CGPA)

Completed my Bachelors in Software Engineering and gained CGPA of 3.36 final GPA of 3.48 and Scored 91 marks in Final Year
project. During my graduation I've learned a lot of skills and improved not just my personality but my social behavior as well
professional skills of my reputed degree. As final year project I've worked on AI and robotics train object detection model, work with
Tesseract Google OCR, Tensorflow Google's Machine learning framwork, conventional Nural networks and a lot of other
technologies related to AI. My Final report, Software version, Proposal or any related document could be accessed via my website or
via email.

SHIBLEE COLLEGE, SAHIWAL

 $Inter\ in\ Fsc. (Pre.\ Engineering)\ ,\ April\ 2013\ -\ March\ 2015\ (\ \textbf{750/1100}\)$

 Completed Pre Engineering with scholarship form reputed college of Sahiwal that is converted into GC College and University in 2015.

IT VILLAGE School, Sahiwal

Matriculation in Science(Biology), Jan. 2011 - Feb. 2013 (872/1050)

• Earned 83% marks in Matriculation and achieved full funded scholarship in college level as well as awarded with Chief Minister of Punjab Laptop scheme 2014.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Expert in Microsoft Office Suite
- Expert in Python
- Expert in front end tools

- Experience with SQL Database Tools
- Experience of FLUTTER
- Bilingual in English and Urdu
- $\bullet \quad Experience \, of \, Nosql \, Databases \,$
- Experience of AI and robotics
- Further details are available at my Web Portfolio.

Refrences

Safdar Khan 2020

References are provided on demand.

ESUME SAIFDAIR KHAN

Get My Protected Complete Bigraph which contain detail certificates, Degrees and every thing Scan this QR



OR Link

https://www.safdarkhan.ml/protected/

Protected BioGraph Password: **since1997**

